[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fruit juices cause about as much harm to your teeth as Colas do.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a subspecies of giraffe?", "correct_answer": "East African Giraffe", "incorrect_answers": ["Somali Giraffe", "Rothschilds Giraffe", "Kordofan Giraffe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About half of the 26,000 kg diamonds mined annually originate from which continent?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "South America", "Europe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The greatest age to which any man has ever lived is this.", "correct_answer": "120 years", "incorrect_answers": ["134 years", "162 years", "104 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the most villainous cat in the film Cats and Dogs?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Tinkles", "incorrect_answers": ["Mrs. Catamaran", "Mr. Bojangles", "Mrs. Gato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clara Barton was the founder of the American Red Cross, but who founded the International Red Cross in 1863?", "correct_answer": "Henry Dunant", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry Ford", "William Durant", "Alfred Nobel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call the type of economy, where the government has an exclusive control over the production and distribution of goods and services?", "correct_answer": "Centrally planned economy", "incorrect_answers": ["Communal economy", "Market economy", "Transitional economy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The production of maple syrup traditionally starts in what month?", "correct_answer": "February", "incorrect_answers": ["July", "October", "September"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Camerons Titanic was nominated for how many Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "14", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "12", "16"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The popular chat room abbreviation asl or a/s/l stands for age, sex, and location.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Yerkes Observatory in Williams Bay, Wisconsin, established in 1897 by George Ellery Hale, works with a 102 cm (40 inch) refracting telescope.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michael Jordan is often considered the best player the Chicago Bulls ever had but they did not start winning championships until they traded Charles Oakley for this other big man.", "correct_answer": "Bill Cartwright", "incorrect_answers": ["Scotty Pippen", "Dave Corzine", "Dennis Rodman"]}]